[
  {
    "question": "Saturn has __________ number of moons.",
    "options": [
      "64",
      "62",
      "69"
    ],
    "correct": "62"
  },
  {
    "question": "Saturn was first observed by  __________.",
    "options": [
      "Copernicus",
      "William Hershel",
      "Galileo Galilei"
    ],
    "correct": "Galileo Galilei"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not one of Saturn’s moons?",
    "options": [
      "Rhea",
      "Ganymede",
      "Titan"
    ],
    "correct": "Ganymede"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the temperature on the surface of Saturn?",
    "options": [
      "-178C",
      "-158C",
      "-128C"
    ],
    "correct": "-178C"
  },
  {
    "question": "The ring system of Saturn stretches to about _________ km from the planet.",
    "options": [
      "100800",
      "120700",
      "110500"
    ],
    "correct": "120700"
  },
  {
    "question": "Saturn was first recorded by ___________.",
    "options": [
      "Assyrians",
      "William Hershel",
      "Babylonian astronomers"
    ],
    "correct": "Assyrians"
  },
  {
    "question": "The number of spacecrafts that have visited Saturn is _________.",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "4"
    ],
    "correct": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the approximate value of polar diameter of Saturn?",
    "options": [
      "108,000-109,000 km",
      "105,000-106,000 km",
      "112,000-113,000 km"
    ],
    "correct": "108,000-109,000 km"
  },
  {
    "question": "Saturn’s atmosphere comprises of _____ % hydrogen and _______ % helium.",
    "options": [
      "78 & 21",
      "96 & 3",
      "88 & 7"
    ],
    "correct": "96 & 3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Saturn orbits the Sun once every _______ Earth years.",
    "options": [
      "26.4",
      "28.4",
      "29.4"
    ],
    "correct": "29.4"
  },
  {
    "question": "When was Saturn first recorded?",
    "options": [
      "8th century B.C",
      "12th century B.C",
      "6th century B.C"
    ],
    "correct": "8th century B.C"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mass of Saturn?",
    "options": [
      "10^26 kg",
      "10^24 kg",
      "10^20 kg"
    ],
    "correct": "10^26 kg"
  },
  {
    "question": "Saturn has _________ rings.",
    "options": [
      "Less than 20",
      "Between 20 and 30",
      "More than 30"
    ],
    "correct": "More than 30"
  },
  {
    "question": "Saturn comprises of hydrogen, helium and ____________.",
    "options": [
      "Neon",
      "Methane",
      "Argon"
    ],
    "correct": "Methane"
  },
  {
    "question": "The distance of the orbit of Saturn is approximately _____________.",
    "options": [
      "1,426,666,000 km",
      "1,496,777,000 km",
      "1,416,888,000 km"
    ],
    "correct": "1,426,666,000 km"
  }
]